bechlo.com 2015-06-13

# Privacy Policy | Bechlo.com

This privacy policy describes how we handle your personal information. We collect, use, and share personal information to help the Bechlo.com website (“http://www.bechlo.com“) work and to keep it safe (details below). In formal terms, www.bechlo.com, acting itself and through its subsidiaries, is the “data controller” of your personal information. This policy is effective from 23th July 2012.

**Collection:-** Information posted on Bechlo.com is obviously publicly available. We collect and store the following personal information:  
• email address, physical contact information, and (depending on the service used) sometimes financial information;  
• other information, including users IP address and standard web log information.

**Use:-** We use users’ personal information to:  
• provide our services;  
• customize users’ experience, measure interest in our services, and inform users about services and updates;  
• communicate marketing and promotional offers to you;  
• Do other things for users as described when we collect the information.

**Disclosure:-**  
• All information contained by Bechlo.com is treated as strictly confidential and Bechlo.com does not and will not disclose or share such confidential information to / with any external organization.  
• The users’ privacy is very important to us. We do not and shall not at any point in time, either sell or rent users’ personal information to third parties without users’ explicit consent.  
• We may be required from time to time to disclose users’ personal information to Governmental or law enforcing agencies or our regulators, but we will only do so under proper authority.  
• Bechlo.com also reserves the right to make use of the personal information in any investigation or judicial process relating to fraud on account of such transactions during the period Bechlo.com retains such information.  
• We may also disclose personal information to enforce our policies, respond to claims that a posting or other content violates other’s rights, or protects anyone’s rights, property or safety.  
• We may also share personal information with:  
\- Corporate affiliates who help detect or prevent potentially illegal acts and provide joint services (Our corporate affiliates will market  
only to users who ask them to).  
\- Service providers who help with our business operations.  
**Using Information from Bechlo.com**. You may use personal information gathered from Bechlo.com only to follow up with another user about a specific posting, not to send spam/ phishing or collect personal information from someone who hasn’t agreed to that.

**Access, Modification, and Deletion.** You can see, modify or erase your personal information by reviewing your posting or account status page. Contact customer support at admin@bechlo.com to review any personal information we store that is not available on Bechlo.com. This service is provided without taking any charge. We delete personal information when we no longer need it for the purposes we described earlier. We retain personal information as permitted by law to resolve disputes, enforce our policies; and prevent bad guys from coming back.

**Data Security.** We use a number of mechanisms (encryption, passwords, and physical security) to protect the security and integrity of your personal information against unauthorized access and disclosure. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the internet can be guaranteed to be completely secure. So while we strive to protect such information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us and you do so at your own risk. Once any personal information comes into our possession, we will take reasonable steps to protect that information from misuse and loss and from unauthorized access, modification or disclosure.

**Confidentiality of Information.** Users who use any of the features on Bechlo.com agree and accept that they have been fully informed by Bechlo.com that the use of features may lead to publication, to all users of Bechlo.com, of any personal information posted by them while using any specific feature on Bechlo.com. Users further agree that the authenticity of, and consequences from the posting by users of any personal information of themselves or any other person, are the sole responsibility of the user. Users further agree and accept that the terms of the Privacy Policy will be applicable to the use of all features, existing and new. However, the Users agree and accept that confidentiality of information posted on such features has been waived by the Users of such features themselves.

**General.** Bechlo.com.com does NOT allow anyone to use our products or services for the purpose of posting Spam classified ads. If a customer posts Spam classified ads in bechlo.com, his or her account will be terminated. The following spam policy will effective from April 2012.
